SUTANTO

STUDENT



Profile

My full name is Sutanto, I am a college student at Esa Unggul University. My major is Information Technology. I'm currently a typesetting assistant on Line Webtoon now and ever to be an online owner at Reap Store for 1 year. I can operate Adobe Photoshop, and Microsoft well and have basic knowledge of digital marketing. I am seeking a part time, freelance or internship where i can explore my skill and learn for a new experience.

Education

2021 - Present

Esa Unggul University

2018 - 2021

Saint Joseph High School Social Major

Phone:

+62 813 1208 6533

Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/sutanto19

Email Adress:

Sutantow19@gmail.com

Address:

Pondok Ungu Permai Blok AL 14/1, Bekasi

Job Experience

2020-2021 Owner Online Shop Reap Store

- Take a photos and upload products to e-commerce
- Reply to messages from customers

2023-2023 Unity 2D Games

- Create a simple 2D based game system
- Designed and implemented gameplay, control systems, and game logic

Skills

Photoshop Digital Marketing

Microsoft Office C++

Unity

HTML/CSS

Interests

■ Travelling
■ Gaming